[
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is the most acceptable behavior when approaching a \"Wushu Hottie\" in the home?",
    "answers": [
      "Down a shot and say \"I'm gonna hit on her.\"",
      "Break personal space and take a selfie.",
      "Yell \"Lai Lai Lai\" from across the house and coerce her to take a shot.",
      "Ask Wushu Hottie what their kinks are.",
      "Show her your forms knowing full well that your Wushu is trash."
    ],
    "correct": "Show her your forms knowing full well that your Wushu is trash."
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False. If a Wushu stranger comments on the size of the spear in the corner, the correct thing to do is say \"That's what she said.\"",
    "answers": ["True", "False"],
    "correct": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "You notice a Wushu Hottie isn't looking so hot. Which of the following is the correct course of action?",
    "answers": [
      "Offer said hottie a glass of water.",
      "Ignore her/him.",
      "Draw on his/her face.",
      "Take dumb shit photos with them or of them.",
      "Do more wushu."
    ],
    "correct": "Offer said hottie a glass of water."
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False. When showing affection towards Wushu Hottie, the correct response is to engage in cat-like behavior.",
    "answers": ["True", "False"],
    "correct": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "When your Wushu Bro texts you \"Happy Birthday\", but the Wushu Hottie texts you same thing hours later, which of the following is the correct response?",
    "answers": [
      "Ignore your bro.",
      "Text the hottie first on the off chance she likes you.",
      "Respond to your bro first.",
      "Text your bro after texting the Wushu Hottie.",
      "Do more wushu."
    ],
    "correct": "Respond to your bro first."
  },
  {
    "question": "Wushu Hottie expresses she needs help with straight sword, which is the most acceptable thing to do?",
    "answers": [
      "Stand behind Wushu Hottie and guide her through the flower.",
      "Grab a straight sword and show her how to flower.",
      "Ask Isabella for help since your wushu is trash.",
      "Convince Wushu Hottie to do Southern.",
      "Run out of the room because someone has a sword."
    ],
    "correct": "Ask Isabella for help since your wushu is trash."
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False. When Dr. Tay is demonstrating proper massage technique, you should stand menacingly over Wushu Hottie until she agrees to let you practice on her.",
    "answers": ["True", "False"],
    "correct": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "You are out training with Wushu Hottie, and you notice her horse stance isn't correct. Which of the following is the most correct thing to do?",
    "answers": [
      "Kick or smack her butt until she corrects her form.",
      "Scream that her wushu is trash and she needs to get her act together.",
      "Politely tell her what she can fix and resume practice.",
      "Do more wushu.",
      "Quit wushu because your horse stance is also trash."
    ],
    "correct": "Politely tell her what she can fix and resume practice."
  },
  {
    "question": "You want to take a picture with Wushu Hottie at a party. Which of the following is the correct way to ask for a photo?",
    "answers": [
      "Ask? Just get up in there and take a selfie with her shocked and disgusted face.",
      "Do a sneaky selfie from an unflattering angle.",
      "Don't take a photo.",
      "Ask politely if she is ok with taking a photo with you.",
      "Ask to take a photo and once permission is given, grab that hottie by the waist."
    ],
    "correct": "Ask politely if she is ok with taking a photo with you."
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False. Your friend invites you to a practice and you see a Wushu Hottie who is much younger than you. Since she is over 18, you should hit that.",
    "answers": ["True", "False"],
    "correct": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following are appropriate emojis to send to Wushu Hottie's (of the gender which you are attracted to) DM's in response to their hot wushu video?",
    "answers": ["ü§Æ", "üí•", "üòç", "üòò", "üçÜ"],
    "correct": "üí•"
  },
  {
    "question": "You are a Wushu Hottie that is being asked to a movie by a non-wushu hottie. You are in a committed relationship. Which of the following is the most correct response to the question?",
    "answers": [
      "Cheat on your SO.",
      "Go to movie but tell non-wushu hottie that you are in a relationship.",
      "Say you want to go, and you also want to bring your SO with you.",
      "Ignore the bitch, like a boss.",
      "Keep leading on the person for no reason."
    ],
    "correct": "Say you want to go, and you also want to bring your SO with you."
  },
  {
    "question": "Your friend gives you a pillow so that you can sleep. You are in a relationship with a Wushu Hottie and want to engage in carnal activities. All of the following are incorrect things to do, except:",
    "answers": [
      "Question why you are in a relationship with a Wushu Hottie who doesn't have a second pillow.",
      "Grin connivingly at your friend as you drag the pillow into a private room for a night of festivities.",
      "Use the pillow for carnal activities, burn it, and deny it ever existed.",
      "Give the pillow back.",
      "Do more wushu...preferably not on the bed."
    ],
    "correct": "Give the pillow back."
  },
  {
    "question": "You are hanging out your friend and a Wushu Hottie. You are very excited about your new Virus compression briefs and want to show them to everyone. Which is the most correct thing to do?",
    "answers": [
      "Drop your pants unannounced with a proud grin on your face.",
      "Do more wushu with pants on the ground.",
      "Keep your pants on.",
      "Wait till Wushu Hottie leaves the room and then drop your pants.",
      "Do more wushu with pants on."
    ],
    "correct": "Keep your pants on."
  },
  {
    "question": "You are helping Wushu Hottie respond to a thirsty dude who may be a future co-worker. Which of the following is the most correct response to a DM?",
    "answers": [
      "You say you want to meet up again for training in some undefined future time.",
      "You say you want to meet up again within the next 12-hours.",
      "You ignore thirsty dude and ruin any chance of future collaboration.",
      "You follow thirsty dude to South Africa.",
      "You ask to go out for Boba."
    ],
    "correct": "You say you want to meet up again for training in some undefined future time."
  },
  {
    "question": "You believe two Wushu Hotties are dating each other. Which of the following is the most correct way to find out if this is true?",
    "answers": [
      "Ask them directly.",
      "Ask someone else who is close to those two.",
      "Don't ask.",
      "Do more wushu.",
      "Continue to ship them without doing anything about it."
    ],
    "correct": "Ask them directly."
  },
  {
    "question": "You are drunk as fuck in a really loud restaurant, and you have an inkling to talk to a Wushu Hottie with whom you have not spoken in many years. Which of the following is the most appropriate thing to do?",
    "answers": [
      "Do more wushu.",
      "Don't do anything.",
      "Ask a more sober friend to call Wushu Hottie for you.",
      "Call them and proceed to say things they can't hear or understand.",
      "Call the Wushu Hottie's significant other."
    ],
    "correct": "Ask a more sober friend to call Wushu Hottie for you."
  },
  {
    "question": "You are a Wushu Hottie being hit on by another Wushu Hottie at a competition afterparty. Which of the following is the best way to reject him?",
    "answers": [
      "Compare his wushu to a bagel.",
      "Tell him you'll go on a date with him if he makes A-team at the next team trials.",
      "Agree to go on a date with him with no catch.",
      "Do more wushu, but obviously better than him.",
      "Tell him you'd love to get boba with him, and then flake."
    ],
    "correct": "Tell him you'll go on a date with him if he makes A-team at the next team trials."
  },
  {
    "question": "You are interested in a Wushu Hottie. How do you talk to them?",
    "answers": [
      "Go up and say hi confidently.",
      "Let your friends introduce you as godhands.",
      "Do more wushu.",
      "Go say hi awkwardly.",
      "Tell him you have magic hands."
    ],
    "correct": "Go up and say hi confidently."
  },
  {
    "question": "You are using your Wushu Hottie bro's bathroom. You notice there are a lot of female products in there, leading you to suspect that he might be dating someone. Which of the following is the best way to confirm this?",
    "answers": [
      "Do nothing and just silently suspect that he is dating someone.",
      "Just assume that all the feminine products are his.",
      "Ask him if he's dating a specific Wushu Hottie.",
      "Use the feminine products yourself.",
      "Do more wushu in the bathroom."
    ],
    "correct": "Ask him if he's dating a specific Wushu Hottie."
  }
]
